

Stefan Jivalino

IOS DEVELOPER / WEB DEVELOPER

Personal Data

Date of birth : Pontianak, June 9th 1996

Address : Jl. Boulevard Gading

Serpong Apart. M-Town Summarecon Serpong

Contact

(Q)

+62851 5676 0425



stefanjivalino3



stefanjivalino@gmail.com



Stefan Jivalino



stefanjivalino3

Education

Multimedia Nusantara University

Computer Science

Apple Developer Academy

Cohort 3 (Student)

Skills

TECHNICAL SKILL

Swift Javascript PHP Framework

PHP JQuery

CodeIgniter

CSS React JS

Laravel

• Zend

OTHERS

Public Speaking

English

Personal Profile

A highly motivated and experienced technical engineering, specialized in iOS and Website Development. I am currently students of Apple Developer Academy @BINUS and skilled in Swift Programming Language. Additionally, I like to improve myself for the benefit of myself and i am willing to learn anything to help with my skills.

Work Experience

Junior iOS Developer (Students)

Apple Developer Academy @BINUS Februari 2020 - Desember 2020

IT Specialist / .Net Programmer

PT. INSPIRO (Internship) Juli 2017 - Oktober 2017

Website Developer

Ikatan Koko Cici Jakarta Mei 2018 - Juni 2019

Head Of Web Development

Ikatan Koko Cici Jakarta Juni 2019 - Sekarang

PHP Programmer

PT Square Gate One Desember 2018 - Maret 2020

Achievment

4th Bali International Choir Festival 2015

• Gold Medalist Folklore Category

• Silver Medalist Musica Sacra Cetegory

3rd Singapore International Choral Festival 2016

· Gold Medalist Folklore Category

• Silver Medalist Musica Sacra Cetegory

Pemilihan Koko Cici Jakarta 2018

• Finalis Top 16



Stefan Jivalino

IOS DEVELOPER / WEB DEVELOPER

iOS Development



SKINS - Skincare Analyzer

An app that helps skincare users analyze the ingredients of their current skincare products and lists the beneficial and irritanting ingredients based on their skin type, and recommends users product alternatives.







Chabudd - Your Workout Buddy

An app that improve studentsphysical activities with simple workout









Tourneo

Tourneo is a badminton tournament companion app, helping admins with all the recording and result sharing.

App Demo







Beer Pong: ToD

Beer Pong: ToD is a challenging app that adapting two party game into one app, beer pong and truth or dare. There will be two players compete playing beer pong and the lose one must do the truth or dare.

App Demo





Web Development



Blue Lane Coffe

Blue Lane Coffee is a Coffee Shop run by PT Prime Restaurant Indonesia (KINO)

https://www.bluelanecoffee.com/

Travellino Tour

Creating an information website for Travellino
Travellino
Tour & Travel

https://www.travellinotour.com/



Teh Sariwang

Manage to build two pages for teh sariwangi website page.

https://www.tehsariwangi.com/



KOKO CICI Koko Cici Jakarta

Build organization website for Koko Cici Jakarta, a non-profit organization in DKI Jakarta

http://kokocicijakarta.com/